<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kika</title>
    <link>https://Kika-02.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kika</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:46:30 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Kika-02.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Life</title>
      <link>https://Kika-02.github.io/2022/11/my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:46:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Kika-02.github.io/2022/11/my-life/</guid>
      <description>My family my father &amp;ndash; Zhaohua, an auditor
my mother &amp;ndash; Xiaoyan, a teacher
my dog &amp;ndash; Coco, the happiest one in history My friends We have become friends for 13 years !!!
The declious food I tasted in Macao Chili Pub India Garden The Cheesecake Factory Siam Brasserie Wonderwall Coffee Lavish Gourmet One time I was quarantined I took my temperature every day! and drink more water </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://Kika-02.github.io/2021/07/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 07:28:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Kika-02.github.io/2021/07/work/</guid>
      <description>During my internship I helped my teacher, a chief doctor of nutritional department, organize two times of propaganda and education&amp;ndash; one is fouced on growing up for children, and another is focued on chronic obstructive pulmonary disease(COPD) for medical staff of the hospital, including writing activities summary reports.
You can read them &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Keep Growing Up&amp;rdquo; and &amp;quot; Nutriotional Prevention and Treatment of COPD&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTRODUCTION</title>
      <link>https://Kika-02.github.io/2019/09/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:05:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Kika-02.github.io/2019/09/introduction/</guid>
      <description>&amp;mdash; Basic Information 1. Name Chinese Name: Jia Xu English Name: Kika 2. Birthday Gregorian Calendar: 2001.01.24 Lunar Calendar: SPRING FESTIVAL !!! in 2001 (Yes! We SHOULD NOT care about our age NO MATTTER how old we are, because it&amp;rsquo;s an HONOR that shows vigor, power or experience!)
3. Gender &amp;mdash; Female : a Energetic and Creative Girl a Considerate and Elegant Lady 4. Hometowm &amp;mdash; Yancheng City, Jiangsu Province, China the Largest city in Jiangsu a Coastal city in the Eastern-Central part of China with the largest Red-crowned Crane Nature Reserve of China 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CURRICULUM VITAE</title>
      <link>https://Kika-02.github.io/2019/09/curriculum-vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 07:28:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Kika-02.github.io/2019/09/curriculum-vitae/</guid>
      <description>EDUCATION BACKGROUND Macau University of Science and Technology(MUST) &amp;mdash; 09/2019-08/2023 Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Food and Nutritional Sciences AWARDS on the &amp;ldquo;Dean&amp;rsquo;s Honor List&amp;rdquo; of Faculty of Medicine of the academic year 2020/2021 INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE 1. Yancheng NO.1 Peeple&amp;rsquo;s Hospital &amp;mdash; Inter of the Nutrition Department, 07/2022 - 08/2022
Followed the Director of the Nutrition Department in outpatient service consultation and expert consultation, sorted out the nutritional needs of inpatients and drew the nutritional spectrum for them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
